

Noach Vandekerckhove

Date of birth: 09/05/2000 | Nationality: Belgian | Gender: Male | Email address:

noachvdk@hotmail.com | Website: https://noachvdk.github.io/ | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/noach-vandekerckhove-0284bb222/

Address: Arthur Coussensstraat 138, 8480, Ichtegem, Belgium (Home)

ABOUT ME

Welcome, I am a Game Developer who is a graduate from Howest University, Belgium, graduating in Digital Arts and Entertainment with a major in Game Development. There I've learned how to program primarily in c++ but I also have experience in c#. I also have experience working in existing engines such as Unity or UE4 but also made an engine capable of recreating qbert. For more of my projects please feel free to take a look at my portfolio website which is linked under contact info. My main interest are in Gameplay programming and AI but I am more than willing to explore different branches within my field.

WORK EXPERIENCE

13/02/2022 - 09/06/2022

INTERN GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER TALEWORLDS ENTERTAINMENT

I worked on the game Mount & Blade 2: Bannerlord. My main responsibilities were the creation of several new features and quests. I also attended daily meetings and worked together with other members of the campaign team and members from other teams such as the design team.

09/2022 - CURRENT Dublin, Ireland

PLATFORM EXPERIENCE ASSOCIATE ACCENTURE

I worked as a Trust and Safety reviewer for a well known client company. My day-to-day responsibilities included but was not limited to investigating and resolving issues regarding content that is reported for account support and/or safety, flag for action, and resolve within agreed-upon turnaround times and standards of quality. I also had to understand and remain up-to-date with everchanging client policies and guidelines, resolve inquires according to defined policies and procedures.

During my time here I was able to improve on my time management skills due to the time sensitive nature of the specific workflows. I was also able to acquire a lot of experience with keeping up to date with a fast paced work environment due to the frequent changes to the guidelines and policies.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

31/07/2018 - 30/09/2022 Kortrijk, Belgium

BACHERLOR DIGITAL ARTS AND ENTERTAINMENT WITH A MAJOR IN GAME DEVELOPMENT Howest

During my time at DAE I have realized that both my interest and talents go out into the Gameplay/AI programming fields within the larger Game Developer industry. Om my portfolio which has been linked (https://noachvdk.github.io/) you can find several projects of mine that showcase some of these skills.

The first 2 projects on the page are showcases of gameplay programming. They are 2 games both in different genres that I created in the Unity and in the Unreal Engine respectively.

The next 2 projects on the portfolio then showcase some AI programming skills such as an AI a with Finite State Machine, Blended steering behaviours and several other interesting AI algorithms and logic. The

other project in turn showcases an implementation I made of the A* algorithm an how that worked in a Nav Mesh.

Address Botenkopersstraat 2, 8500, Kortrijk, Belgium | **Website** https://www.digitalartsandentertainment.be/ |

Field of study Game Development

DIGITAL SKILLS

Programming

C++ | C# | Visual Studio

Engines

Experience in Unreal Engine | Familiar with Unity Engine | Custom Engine

Source control

Github | Perforce | Github Pages | Plastic SCM | SourceTree

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **DUTCH**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C1	C1	C1
FRENCH	B2	B2	B1	B1	B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user